Privacy Policy
==============

Escape to Blue Ridge is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using EscapetoBlueRidge.com. Escape to Blue Ridge will never sell any personally identifiable information obtained from a user to a third party. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit EscapetoBlueRidge.com. 

Escape to Blue Ridge gathers information about its users in order to offer useful and easily accessible online content while providing privacy protection. We may make content or services from other websites including our affiliated or co-branded Websites available to you from links located on EscapetoBlueRidge.com. These other websites are not subject to this Privacy Policy and Escape to Blue Ridge is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those websites. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such website to determine how that site protects your privacy.

**Information We Collect**

**General:** When you subscribe to our email program, reservations, or forum, we will collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, address, telephone information, e-mail address, or opinions. This information is necessary to process your online reservation request to rent a cabin. If you are a repeat customer, you may be asked to update this information. 

**Surveys:** We may conduct occasional online surveys. For example, when you’re within our website, you may see a message offering you the optional opportunity of participating in a survey. These surveys are entirely voluntary and you may easily decline to participate. 

**Website Usage Information:** We automatically collect IP addresses and website usage information from you when you visit our website. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors and subscribers use and navigate our websites on an aggregate basis, including the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to each Web page, and the length of their visits. We use this aggregated website usage information to improve our website services to best serve our customers. 

**How We Use Information Collected** 

We may use information in the following ways: 

* For the purposes for which you specifically provided the information including, for example, to enable us to process, validate and verify reservations, email newsletter, and forum registrations. 
* To send you e-mail notifications about our new or existing products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you. 
* To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services. 

Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information outside of EscapetoBlueRidge.com unless you “opt in” to having your personally identifiable information shared with a company that is not affiliated with us. 

**Your Ability to Choose** 

When you subscribe to EscapetoBlueRidge.com, you can let us know that you do not wish to receive information about new features and special offers by opting out at the time you give us your personally identifiable information.  

**Cookies**

When you visit our website, we may pass cookies to your computer. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site sends to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer, so that the site can deliver content appropriate for you. The cookies that Escape to Blue Ridge uses do not contain any of the users’ personally-identifiable information. Certain features may not work if you’ve chosen to disable cookies in your Web browser. Escape to Blue Ridge uses cookies to collect aggregate information about user behavior so we can improve website navigation and the overall website experience. If you do not want cookies sent to your computer, you can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Then you decide whether or not to accept it. 

**Security**

Personal information, once collected, is never shown on the website. It may be emailed only to the address provided along with the information, but never to a different address, even one believed to be a new address for the same person. 

**Policy Modifications** 

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. 

**Comments and Questions** 

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us at info@EscapetoBlueRidge.com
